Demir Sanal

5830 SW 100th St, Miami, FL 33156

(305)-542-8895 demir.sanal@hotmail.com

LinkedIn | GitHub

Summary

Entry level web developer and data analyst with experience writing semantic, forward-looking code and visualizing data in an applicable and insightful manner. Helped small businesses in the education industry develop stronger curriculum plans and uniformed data collections processes, resulting in higher client satisfaction and increased sales success. Knowledge of building responsive, intuitive and secure web applications.

Skills

HTML5 MERN Stack Google Studio CSS3 MySQL MongoDB User Authentication Git JavaScript (ES6+) **j**Query Adobe Creative Cloud Heroku **API Interaction** Elementor Linting Progressive Web Applications Continuous Integration **CSS** Frameworks: -Bootstrap WordPress Unit Testing **Functional Testing Data Structures** -Materialize Turkish -Bulma Spanish

Professional Experience

Prepory Coaching Group - Data Analytics and Web Development

Iune 2020 - Present

- Automated data collection processes and curated informative data studios for our institutional partners
- Analyzed CRM reports to provide data-driven insights focused on improving sales techniques and product models
- Developing a web portal to fit client needs and centralize client-company interactions
- Maintain and improve our website using Wordpress through functional and client-oriented UI/UX design

Collegiate Scholars Program - Office Assistant

October 2019 - February 2020

- Empowered Chicago youth through the expansion of college access resources by means of workshops, information sessions and educational events
- Worked collaboratively to design and plan curriculums that were engaging and effectively prepared our scholars for navigating college admissions
- Collecting and organized parent and student information to be used for email campaigns and communications
- Expanded the reach of our services by translating informational materials to Spanish

Starbucks Corporation - Barista

April 2020 - Present

- Cooperate with fellow baristas to provide quality service to our customers in a time-conscious manner
- Utilize Drive-Through Order and Point of Sale systems with a customer-focused attitude
- Ensure customer satisfaction by fostering consumer relations, brand loyalty and a positive product image

Education

Certification of Completion | University of Miami Coding Bootcamp Undergraduate | University of Chicago High School Diploma | Gulliver Preparatory School Expected March 2021 September 2019 - February 2020 May 2019